<resources>
    <string name="app_name">UVCE Connect</string>
    <string name="open_navigation_drawer">Open Navigation Drawer</string>
    <string name="close_navigation_drawer">Close Navigation Drawer</string>
    <string name="title_activity_about_uvce">about_uvce</string>


    <!--HACK! DONT CHANGE THE NAME, Feel free to change the value!-->
    <string name="arch">Architecture</string>
    <string name="cse">Computer Science and Engineering</string>
    <string name="ce">Civil Engineering</string>
    <string name="eee">Electronic and Electrical Engineering</string>
    <string name="ece">Electronics and Communication Engineering</string>
    <string name="ise">Information Science and Engineering</string>
    <string name="me">Mechanical Engineering</string>
    <string name="download">Download</string>

    <string-array name="branch_array">
        <item>@string/arch</item>
        <item>@string/cse</item>
        <item>@string/ce</item>
        <item>@string/ece</item>
        <item>@string/eee</item>
        <item>@string/ise</item>
        <item>@string/me</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="semester_array">
        <item>1</item>
        <item>2</item>
        <item>3</item>
        <item>4</item>
        <item>5</item>
        <item>6</item>
        <item>7</item>
        <item>8</item>
        <item>9</item>
        <item>10</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="year_array">
        <item>1</item>
        <item>2</item>
        <item>3</item>
        <item>4</item>
        <item>5</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="priority_array">
        <item>Priority</item>
        <item>Non-Priority</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="disclaimer">
        UVCE Connect has made honest effort to gather document from various departments.
        The validation of such documents may vary along with time.
        We appreciate users to contribute towards the same.
    </string>

    <string name="about_uvce_card1">
        UVCE then called ‘College of Engineering’ was established at Bengaluru in 1917 just a year after the University of Mysore was established, giving a fillip to higher education and to enable the students of Mysore State to play their part in the Engineering field.

    </string>
    <string name="about_uvce_card2">
        Initially, two branches of engineering namely, Civil and Mechanical Engineering were started. College of Engineering (UVCE) was the 5th Engineering College of the country and first in the Princely State of Mysore.
    </string>
    <string name="about_uvce_card3">
                UVCE currently offers \n\n
        1.	Seven Undergraduate (B.E/B.Arch) \n
        2.	Twenty-Four Postgraduate (M.E/M.Arch.) \n
        3.	Three Part time BE evening under graduate courses. \n
        4.	M.Sc. (Engineering) byResearch, \n
        5.	Three-Year full time Ph.D., \n
        6.	Four-Year part time Ph.D. programmes in all disciplines. \n
        7.	Ph.D. (QIP) programme in Civil Engineering\n \nThe total intake of the college is about 1200 students a year.
    </string>


    <string name="title_activity_associations">
        ASSOCIATIONS
    </string>
    <string name="title_activity_academics">
    Question Papers and Syllabus
    </string>
    <string name="alumini_card1">
            Alumni are the vital asset for any educational institution. UVCE being a century old college finds its alumni spread widely across globe.
    </string>
    <string name="alumini_card2">
        Alumni association aims to gather its strong alumni network and build a better UVCE with its various initiatives like, \n\n
    1.	Lecture series \n
    2.	Providing scholarship \n
    3.	Corpus funds \n
    4.	Awarding achievers \n
    5.	Planning Centenary building \n
    6.	Community service
    </string>
    <string name="alumini_card3">
    The alumni association strives to keep its members informed about the activities that happen in the college through its newsletter. \n\nWebsite: http://uvcealumni.org/index.html
    </string>


    <string name="foundation_card1">
             The UVCE Foundation was created by alumni, faculty and well-wishers of UVCE in 2003 to help in restoring the glory of UVCE.
    </string>
    <string name="foundation_card2">
        It has members from around the world and has already executed various projects at UVCE to address immediate needs of the students of UVCE.
    </string>
    <string name="foundation_card3">
    UVCE Foundation has been growing in strength ever since its inception and has been widely recognized as a strong support from the college authorities. The objective of the Foundation is to restore the ‘top-ten’ status the college.\n\nWebsite: http://uvcefoundation.org
    </string>


    <string name="vision_card1">
            VisionUVCE is a group of UVCE alumni who are focussed on \"Giving Back to UVCE\" by creating awareness among the strong alumni and make them understand the potential that the creation of an alumni group, working for the betterment of college brings about.
    </string>
    <string name="vision_card2">
         It is VU\'s responsibility to make sure, the flag of our alma mater flies high in the air and also as proud alumni of this college, there is a need to take part in the operations involved with the institution.
    </string>
    <string name="vision_card3">
    Major programs held under VISION UVCE:\n\n
    1	Sampada – A monthly magazine that offers you a ride though UVCE\n
    2	VU scholarship – Every year scholarships are provided to those in need\n
    3	VU champs – Recognition of efforts of Student Volunteers\n
    4	Parichaya – A detailed profile of UVCE’s great alumni\n
    5	Samvaada – Occasional meet between alumnus, current staff and students\n
    6	VU also supports and funds various student initiatives which seems promising in terms of idea and its reach. It\'s also involved in taking care of student\’s utility in campus by funding to the required cause. VU raises its fund from alumni of UVCE.
    </string>
    <string name="vision_card4">
        Website:  http://www.visionuvce.in \n\nEmail: contact@visionuvce.in
    </string>


    <string name="placement_card1">
        Training and Placement Office is the power house of UVCE where, Student coordinators take the responsibility to interact with companies under the guidance of Placement Officer Dr. Thriveni. Placement Office was established in the year 1989, and has been consistently working as a liaison between the industry and students in order to fulfil the ambition of the students in getting the right job.
    </string>
    <string name="placement_card2">
        About 90% of our students are placed in globally recognized companies with attractive offers. Batch of 2016 witnessed an all-time record of grabbing around 1060 offers.
    </string>
    <string name="placement_card3">
        Email: info@campusuvce.in  \nWebsite: http://campusuvce.in/
    </string>


    <string name="uvce_jaathre">
         As the name indicates, it\'s a colourful one day event organised by 2nd year students during the month of Oct every year. During this event various collegiate clubs\’ setup their stall at quadrangle of main campus and conduct fun games, thereby helping freshers to know about UVCE.
    </string>
    <string name="fiesta">
        It\'s a one day intra collegiate Cultural fest of UVCE organised by 3rd year students in odd semester. It\'s a Cultural extravaganza which accelerates UVCEians to participate in widespread events. Students from every department of UVCE participate in this fest.
    </string>
    <string name="civista">
        This event is similar to fiesta but this being celebrated by Civil Students at Jnana Bharathi campus. Civista is the annual Cultural fest of Civil department and is organised by 3rd year students. It attracts huge number of participants from the Bangalore University campus.
    </string>
    <string name="esportivo">
        Sports has a high calibre in UVCE. The craze setup for football and cricket is everlasting in the century old college. Esportivo is a week-long event organised by sports geeks to uphold the sportsmanship sprit among various teams across Bengaluru.
    </string>
    <string name="milagro">
        MILAGRO is the biggest cultural festival in UVCE organised by final year students which spans over two days. However, the entire week will be called as Milagro Week and various events are held to entertain the students. With the history of two decades, it provides a platform where every individual in college comes together to create a difference. It upholds the pride of UVCE and culture of Karnataka. It has always been dealt with grandeur and festivity.
    </string>
    <string name="kagada">
        It\'s a National level technical symposium, organised by Team IEEE UVCE. Students across the country take part in this event where they get to showcase their technical knowledge and research by means of Paper and Poster presentation. The best paper and posters are awarded.
    </string>
    <string name="inspiron">
        Inspiron is an inter college technical fest organized by The Training and Placement Office, UVCE. It is an entrepreneurship and management extravaganza which has various events that requires one to showcase technical, entrepreneurship and managerial skills.  It is conducted every year in odd semester.
    </string>
    <string name="impetus">
        IMPETUS is a National Level Technical Extravaganza organized by IEEE UVCE. IMPETUS is a technical fest designed for a change and with a vivid difference. Unlike other fests, every year this fest goes out with a message for the engineers. The fest was themed after Engineering for Society followed by Innovation and Entrepreneurship in 2013. This 2 day long fest has always had a diverse participation from all over the country. Over the years IMPETUS has emerged to be one of Bengaluru\'s top technical fests.
    </string>
    <string name="title_activity_admin__page">Admin Access</string>
    <string name="title_activity_admin__add__content">Add Content</string>
</resources>
