<resources>
    <string name="app_name">UVCE Connect</string>
    <string name="open_navigation_drawer">Open Navigation Drawer</string>
    <string name="close_navigation_drawer">Close Navigation Drawer</string>


    <!--HACK! DONT CHANGE THE NAME, Feel free to change the value!-->
    <string name="arch">Architecture</string>
    <string name="cse">Computer Science and Engineering</string>
    <string name="ce">Civil Engineering</string>
    <string name="eee">Electrical and Electronics Engineering</string>
    <string name="ece">Electronics and Communication Engineering</string>
    <string name="ise">Information Science and Engineering</string>
    <string name="me">Mechanical Engineering</string>
    <string name="download">Download</string>
    <string name="fill_fields">Please fill all fields to register</string>
    <string name="fields_properly">Please fill valid information to register</string>
    <string name="invalid_register">Kindly enter a valid registration number and try again</string>

    <string name="click_here_to_download"><u>Click here to download </u> </string>

    <string-array name="branch_array">
        <item>@string/arch</item>
        <item>@string/cse</item>
        <item>@string/ce</item>
        <item>@string/ece</item>
        <item>@string/eee</item>
        <item>@string/ise</item>
        <item>@string/me</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="semester_array">
        <item>1</item>
        <item>2</item>
        <item>3</item>
        <item>4</item>
        <item>5</item>
        <item>6</item>
        <item>7</item>
        <item>8</item>
        <item>9</item>
        <item>10</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="year_array">
        <item>1</item>
        <item>2</item>
        <item>3</item>
        <item>4</item>
        <item>5</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="priority_array">
        <item>Priority</item>
        <item>Non-Priority</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="disclaimer">
        UVCE Connect has made honest effort to gather document from various departments.
        The validation of such documents may vary along with time.
        We appreciate users to contribute towards the same.
    </string>

    <!--<string name="about_uvce_card1">-->
    <!--UVCE then called ‘College of Engineering’ was established at Bengaluru in 1917 just a year after the University of Mysore was established, giving a fillip to higher education and to enable the students of Mysore State to play their part in the Engineering field.-->

    <!--</string>-->
    <!--<string name="about_uvce_card2">-->
    <!--Initially, two branches of engineering namely, Civil and Mechanical Engineering were started. College of Engineering (UVCE) was the 5th Engineering College of the country and first in the Princely State of Mysore.-->
    <!--</string>-->
    <!--<string name="about_uvce_card3">-->
    <!--UVCE currently offers \n\n-->
    <!--1.	Seven Undergraduate (B.E/B.Arch) \n-->
    <!--2.	Twenty-Four Postgraduate (M.E/M.Arch.) \n-->
    <!--3.	Three Part time BE evening under graduate courses. \n-->
    <!--4.	M.Sc. (Engineering) byResearch, \n-->
    <!--5.	Three-Year full time Ph.D., \n-->
    <!--6.	Four-Year part time Ph.D. programmes in all disciplines. \n-->
    <!--7.	Ph.D. (QIP) programme in Civil Engineering\n \nThe total intake of the college is about 1200 students a year.-->
    <!--</string>-->


    <string name="title_activity_associations">
        ASSOCIATIONS
    </string>
    <string name="title_activity_academics">
    Question Papers and Syllabus
    </string>
    <!--<string name="alumini_card1">-->
    <!--Alumni are the vital asset for any educational institution. UVCE being a century old college finds its alumni spread widely across globe.-->
    <!--</string>-->
    <!--<string name="alumini_card2">-->
    <!--Alumni association aims to gather its strong alumni network and build a better UVCE with its various initiatives like, \n\n-->
    <!--1.	Lecture series \n-->
    <!--2.	Providing scholarship \n-->
    <!--3.	Corpus funds \n-->
    <!--4.	Awarding achievers \n-->
    <!--5.	Planning Centenary building \n-->
    <!--6.	Community service-->
    <!--</string>-->
    <!--<string name="alumini_card3">-->
    <!--The alumni association strives to keep its members informed about the activities that happen in the college through its newsletter. \n\nWebsite: http://uvcealumni.org/index.html-->
    <!--</string>-->


    <!--<string name="foundation_card1">-->
    <!--The UVCE Foundation was created by alumni, faculty and well-wishers of UVCE in 2003 to help in restoring the glory of UVCE.-->
    <!--</string>-->
    <!--<string name="foundation_card2">-->
    <!--It has members from around the world and has already executed various projects at UVCE to address immediate needs of the students of UVCE.-->
    <!--</string>-->
    <!--<string name="foundation_card3">-->
    <!--UVCE Foundation has been growing in strength ever since its inception and has been widely recognized as a strong support from the college authorities. The objective of the Foundation is to restore the ‘top-ten’ status the college.\n\nWebsite: http://uvcefoundation.org-->
    <!--</string>-->


    <!--<string name="vision_card1">-->
    <!--VisionUVCE is a group of UVCE alumni who are focussed on \"Giving Back to UVCE\" by creating awareness among the strong alumni and make them understand the potential that the creation of an alumni group, working for the betterment of college brings about.-->
    <!--</string>-->
    <!--<string name="vision_card2">-->
    <!--It is VU\'s responsibility to make sure, the flag of our alma mater flies high in the air and also as proud alumni of this college, there is a need to take part in the operations involved with the institution.-->
    <!--</string>-->
    <!--<string name="vision_card3">-->
    <!--Major programs held under VISION UVCE:\n\n-->
    <!--1	Sampada – A monthly magazine that offers you a ride though UVCE\n-->
    <!--2	VU scholarship – Every year scholarships are provided to those in need\n-->
    <!--3	VU champs – Recognition of efforts of Student Volunteers\n-->
    <!--4	Parichaya – A detailed profile of UVCE’s great alumni\n-->
    <!--5	Samvaada – Occasional meet between alumnus, current staff and students\n-->
    <!--6	VU also supports and funds various student initiatives which seems promising in terms of idea and its reach. It\'s also involved in taking care of student\’s utility in campus by funding to the required cause. VU raises its fund from alumni of UVCE.-->
    <!--</string>-->
    <!--<string name="vision_card4">-->
    <!--Website:  http://www.visionuvce.in \n\nEmail: contact@visionuvce.in-->
    <!--</string>-->


    <!--<string name="placement_card1">-->
    <!--Training and Placement Office is the power house of UVCE where, Student coordinators take the responsibility to interact with companies under the guidance of Placement Officer Dr. Thriveni. Placement Office was established in the year 1989, and has been consistently working as a liaison between the industry and students in order to fulfil the ambition of the students in getting the right job.-->
    <!--</string>-->
    <!--<string name="placement_card2">-->
    <!--About 90% of our students are placed in globally recognized companies with attractive offers. Batch of 2016 witnessed an all-time record of grabbing around 1060 offers.-->
    <!--</string>-->
    <!--<string name="placement_card3">-->
    <!--Email: info@campusuvce.in  \nWebsite: http://campusuvce.in/-->
    <!--</string>-->


    <string name="uvce_jaathre">
         As the name indicates, it\'s a colourful one day event organised by 2nd year students during the month of Oct every year. During this event various collegiate clubs\’ setup their stall at quadrangle of main campus and conduct fun games, thereby helping freshers to know about UVCE.
    </string>
    <string name="fiesta">
        It\'s a one day intra collegiate Cultural fest of UVCE organised by 3rd year students in odd semester. It\'s a Cultural extravaganza which accelerates UVCEians to participate in widespread events. Students from every department of UVCE participate in this fest.
    </string>
    <string name="civista">
        This event is similar to fiesta but this being celebrated by Civil Students at Jnana Bharathi campus. Civista is the annual Cultural fest of Civil department and is organised by 3rd year students. It attracts huge number of participants from the Bangalore University campus.
    </string>
    <string name="esportivo">
        Sports has a high calibre in UVCE. The craze setup for football and cricket is everlasting in the century old college. Esportivo is a week-long event organised by sports geeks to uphold the sportsmanship sprit among various teams across Bengaluru.
    </string>
    <string name="milagro">
        MILAGRO is the biggest cultural festival in UVCE organised by final year students which spans over two days. However, the entire week will be called as Milagro Week and various events are held to entertain the students. With the history of two decades, it provides a platform where every individual in college comes together to create a difference. It upholds the pride of UVCE and culture of Karnataka. It has always been dealt with grandeur and festivity.
    </string>
    <string name="kagada">
        It\'s a National level technical symposium, organised by Team IEEE UVCE. Students across the country take part in this event where they get to showcase their technical knowledge and research by means of Paper and Poster presentation. The best paper and posters are awarded.
    </string>
    <string name="inspiron">
        Inspiron is an inter college technical fest organized by The Training and Placement Office, UVCE. It is an entrepreneurship and management extravaganza which has various events that requires one to showcase technical, entrepreneurship and managerial skills.  It is conducted every year in odd semester.
    </string>
    <string name="impetus">
        IMPETUS is a National Level Technical Extravaganza organized by IEEE UVCE. IMPETUS is a technical fest designed for a change and with a vivid difference. Unlike other fests, every year this fest goes out with a message for the engineers. The fest was themed after Engineering for Society followed by Innovation and Entrepreneurship in 2013. This 2 day long fest has always had a diverse participation from all over the country. Over the years IMPETUS has emerged to be one of Bengaluru\'s top technical fests.
    </string>
    <string name="title_activity_admin__page">Admin Access</string>
    <string name="title_activity_admin__add__content">Add Content</string>
    <string name="title_activity_admin__add__delete">Admin Operations</string>

    <string name="privacy">
        This is an unofficial app of UVCE. Read Declaration in About Page.\n
\n
UVCE CONNECT Android Application (\"we\" or \"us\") understand that you care about your personal information and therefore we take the privacy of your information very seriously. Our Privacy Policy is designed to tell you about our practices regarding the collection, use and disclosure of information that you may provide us with while using our mobile application. By using our application, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy. If we make any changes to our privacy policy we will update the privacy policy here with the last revised date at the bottom of the Privacy Policy.\n
\n
This privacy policy has been compiled to better serve those who are concerned with how their \'Personally Identifiable Information\' (PII) is being used online. PII, as described in US privacy law and information security, is information that can be used on its own or with other information to identify, contact, or locate a single person, or to identify an individual in context. Please read our privacy policy carefully to get a clear understanding of how we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your Personally Identifiable Information in accordance with our website.\n
\n
\n
Scope\n
\n
This Privacy Policy governs the information we collect using the UVCE CONNECT Android application and only that. We are not responsible for any information you pass into any third-party websites from the link on this application, and this Privacy Policy does not govern any other website.\n
\n
What personal information do we collect from the people that use our app?\n
\n
We collect personal information such as your name, registration number, email address, contact number, from you at the point when you sign in or sign up for an account.\n
When you use our application, we collect additional information such as your device model/manufacturer and phone language. We \"DO NOT\" access your location or demographics data such as your age and gender via third party analytics tool for analytics purposes.\n
\n
 \n
\n
When do we collect information?\n
\n
We collect information from you when you try to download any form of data from the app and when you sent feedback from the app.\n
\n
How do we use your information?\n
\n
We may use the information we collect from you when you register, download any data from us, respond to a survey or promotional communication, surf the application, or use certain other features in the following ways:\n
\n
      • To improve our application in order to better serve you.\n
\n
      • To allow us to better service you in responding to your customer service requests.\n
\n
\n
 \n
How do we protect your information?\n
\n
We have implemented administrative and technical safeguards we believe these are sufficient to protect the confidentiality, integrity. However, we believe that a determined attacker with sufficient resources could defeat those safeguards and may, as a result, gain access to the information we seek to protect. This Site may contains links and references to other websites. Please be aware that this Privacy Policy does not apply to those websites. We cannot be responsible for the privacy policies and practices of sites that are not operated by us, even if you access them via the Site. We recommend that you check the policy of each site you visit and contact its owner or operator if you have any concerns or questions. In addition, if you came to this site via a third party site, we cannot be responsible for the privacy policies and practices of the owners or operators of that third party site and recommend that you check the policy of that third party site and contact its owner or operator if you have any concerns or questions.\n
\n
      • We do not use vulnerability scanning and/or scanning to PCI standards.\n
\n
      • We only provide articles and information. We never ask for credit card numbers.\n
\n
      • We only provide articles and information.\n
\n
\n
\n
Third-party disclosure\n
\n
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your Personally Identifiable Information.\n
 \n
\n
Third-party links\n
\n
We do not include or offer third-party products or services on our website.\n
\n
 \n
\n
Google\n
\n
Google\'s advertising requirements can be summed up by Google\'s Advertising Principles. They are put in place to provide a positive experience for users. You can read the AdWords Policy here.\n
\n
We use Google AdSense Advertising on our website.\n
\n
\n
Google, as a third-party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Google\'s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on previous visits to our site and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt-out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google Ad and Content Network privacy policy.\n
\n
\n
We have implemented the following:\n
\n
      • DoubleClick Platform Integration\n
\n
 We, along with third-party vendors such as Google use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookies) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) or other third-party identifiers together to compile data regarding user interactions with ad impressions and other ad service functions as they relate to our website.\n
\n
\n
Opting out:\n
Users can set preferences for how Google advertises to you using the Google Ad Settings page. Alternatively, you can opt out by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative Opt Out page or by using the Google Analytics Opt Out Browser add on.\n
\n
 \n
\n
California Online Privacy Protection Act\n
\n
CalOPPA is the first state law in the nation to require commercial websites and online services to post a privacy policy. The law\'s reach stretches well beyond California to require any person or company in the United States (and conceivably the world) that operates websites collecting Personally Identifiable Information from California consumers to post a conspicuous privacy policy on its website stating exactly the information being collected and those individuals or companies with whom it is being shared. - See more at: http://consumercal.org/california-online-privacy-protection-act-caloppa/#sthash.0FdRbT51.dpuf\n
\n
\n
According to CalOPPA, we agree to the following:\n
\n
Users can visit our site anonymously.\n
\n
Once this privacy policy is created, we will add a link to it on our home page or as a minimum, on the first significant page after entering our website.\n
\n
Our Privacy Policy link includes the word \'Privacy\' and can be easily be found on the page specified above.\n
\n
\n
You will be notified of any Privacy Policy changes:\n
\n
      • On our Privacy Policy Page\n
\n
Can change your personal information:\n
\n
      • By emailing us\n
\n
\n
How does our site handle Do Not Track signals?\n
\n
We honor Do Not Track signals and Do Not Track, plant cookies, or use advertising when a Do Not Track (DNT) browser mechanism is in place.\n
\n
\n
Does our site allow third-party behavioral tracking?\n
\n
It\'s also important to note that we do not allow third-party behavioral tracking\n
\n
 \n
\n
COPPA (Children Online Privacy Protection Act)\n
        \n
When it comes to the collection of personal information from children under the age of 13 years old, the Children\'s Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) puts parents in control. The Federal Trade Commission, United States\' consumer protection agency, enforces the COPPA Rule, which spells out what operators of websites and online services must do to protect children\'s privacy and safety online.\n
\n
 \n
\n
We do not specifically market to children under the age of 13 years old.\n
\n
 \n
\n
Fair Information Practices\n
\n
The Fair Information Practices Principles form the backbone of privacy law in the United States and the concepts they include have played a significant role in the development of data protection laws around the globe. Understanding the Fair Information Practice Principles and how they should be implemented is critical to comply with the various privacy laws that protect personal information.\n
 \n
\n
In order to be in line with Fair Information Practices we will take the following responsive action, should a data breach occur:\n
\n
We will notify you via email\n
\n
      • Within 1 business day\n
\n
\n
We also agree to the Individual Redress Principle which requires that individuals have the right to legally pursue enforceable rights against data collectors and processors who fail to adhere to the law. This principle requires not only that individuals have enforceable rights against data users, but also that individuals have recourse to courts or government agencies to investigate and/or prosecute non-compliance by data processors.\n
\n
 \n
\n
CAN SPAM Act \n
\n
The CAN-SPAM Act is a law that sets the rules for commercial email, establishes requirements for commercial messages, gives recipients the right to have emails stopped from being sent to them, and spells out tough penalties for violations.\n
 \n
\n
We collect your email address in order to:\n
\n
      • Send information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions\n
\n
      • Track the application usage and all related application statistics.\n
\n
\n
To be in accordance with CANSPAM, we agree to the following:\n
\n
      • Not use false or misleading subjects or email addresses.\n
\n
      • Identify the message as an advertisement in some reasonable way.\n
        \n
      • Include the physical address of our business or site headquarters.\n
\n
      • Monitor third-party email marketing services for compliance, if one is used.\n
\n
      • Honor opt-out/unsubscribe requests quickly.\n
\n
      • Allow users to unsubscribe by using the link at the bottom of each email.\n
\n
\n
If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, you can email us at\n
\n
      • Follow the instructions at the bottom of each email.\n
\n
and we will promptly remove you from ALL correspondence.\n
\n
Contacting Us\n
If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy, you may contact us using the information below.\n
\n
Mail ID\n
uvceconnect@gmail.com
    </string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->

    <!--<string name="chethana_card1">-->
    <!--ನಾವು ಕನ್ನಡಿಗರು, ವಿಶಾಲ ಹೃದಯವನ್ನು ಹೊಂದವರು, ಜಗತ್ತಿನ ಮೂಲೆ-ಮೂಲೆಗಳಿಂದ ಹರಿದುಬರುವ ಜನರನ್ನು ತನ್ನ ಓಡಿಲಲ್ಲಿ ಸಾಕಿ ಸಲಹುವವರು. ಈ ಸಲಹುವಿಕೆ ಹೆಚ್ಚಾಯಿತೇನೋ, ಬೆಂಗಳೂರಿನಲ್ಲಿ ಕನ್ನಡಿಗರೇ ಅಲ್ಪಸಂಖ್ಯಾತರಾಗಿದ್ದಾರೆ. ಕನ್ನಡತನ ಎಂಬುದು ಮುಗಿದುಹೋದ ಅಧ್ಯಾಯವಾಗತೊಡಗಿದೆ. ಇಡೀಯ ಜಗತ್ತಿನಲ್ಲಿ ಅಂಗೈಯಷ್ಟು ಅಗಲ ಜಾಗದಲ್ಲಿ ಮಾತ್ರ ಕನ್ನಡ ಉಸಿರಾಡುತ್ತಿದೆ. ಕನ್ನಡವನ್ನು ಬಳಸುವ, ಉಳಿಸುವ, ಬೆಳೆಸುವ ಕೆಲಸ ಮಾಡಬೇಕಿದೆ.-->
    <!--</string>-->
    <!--<string name="chethana_card2">-->
    <!--ನಮ್ಮೆಲ್ಲರಲ್ಲೂ ಕನ್ನಡಾಭಿಮಾನ ಭೂದಿ ಮುಚ್ಚಿದ ಕೆಂಡದಂತಿದೆ. ಹಾಗೆಯೇ ನಮ್ಮ ಸಂಸ್ಥೆಯಲ್ಲಿ ಕನ್ನಡಾಭಿಮಾನಿಗಳು ಹರಿದು ಹಂಚಿಹೋಗಿದ್ದಾರೆ, ಹಾಗೂ ಕನ್ನಡವೇ ಉಸಿರು ಎಂದು ಬದುಕುತ್ತಿರುವವರು ಎಲೆಮರೆಯ ಕಾಯಿಯಂತಾಗಿದ್ದಾರೆ. ಇವರನ್ನೆಲ್ಲಾ ಒಂದುಗೂಡಿಸುವ ಪ್ರಯತ್ನ ಚೇತನದ ಉದ್ದೇಶ. \n\nಕನ್ನಡದ ಏಳಿಗೆಗಾಗಿ, ಅದರ ಸಾರ್ವಬೌಮತೆಗಾಗಿ , ಕನ್ನಡಾಂಬೆ  ಸೇವೆಗಾಗಿ ಹುಟ್ಟಿಕೊಂಡ ಗುಂಪು ಚೇತನ. ಇಲ್ಲಿ ಸಾಹಿತ್ಯ ಉತ್ಖನನ, ಸಂಗೀತ ಸಮರ್ಪಣಾ ಹಾಗೂ ವಯಕ್ತಿಕ ಏಳಿಗೆಗೆ ಶ್ರಮಿಸಲಾಗುತ್ತದೆ.-->
    <!--</string>-->
    <!--<string name="chethana_card3">-->
    <!--ಸಂಪರ್ಕಿಸಿ: - Sachin  (+91 96110 17485) \n\n-->
    <!--ಮಿಂಚಂಚೆ:-  uvcekannadasanga.chetana@gmail.com-->
    <!--</string>-->

    <!--<string name="chakravyuha_card1">-->
    <!--Life is full of surprises, Adventure is a part and parcel of engineering life. In this limited 4years an engineering student would have experienced lot of unforgettable moments. To quench one\'s thirst for Adventure \"Chakravyuha\" the trekking club of UVCE was started by students.-->
    <!--Club usually holds 2 trekking drives in each semester. Starting point of every trek being UVCE, it tries to explore trekking spots across Bengaluru within a tight budget and give students an adventure experience.-->
    <!--</string>-->
    <!--<string name="chakravyuha_card2">-->
    <!--The recent treks being: \n\n-->
    <!--1.	Kunthi betta \n-->
    <!--2.	Makalidurga \n-->
    <!--3.	Tadiyandanmol \n-->
    <!--4.	Chanarayanna durga-->
    <!--</string>-->
    <!--<string name="chakravyuha_card3">-->
    <!--Contact:- Chandan  (+91 87222 53181)-->
    <!--</string>-->

    <!--&lt;!&ndash;<string name="vinimaya_card1">&ndash;&gt;-->
    <!--&lt;!&ndash;Books are a collection of enormous amount of knowledge and guidance in a compressed form; it is a vital asset for the mankind. ‘VINIMAYA’ meaning ‘Sharing’ in Kannada, works on this very basic principle. Books that a student has can be shared with the club and the books that VINIMAYA has can be borrowed by the students. There\'s no worry if one doesn\'t have a book to share.&ndash;&gt;-->
    <!--&lt;!&ndash;</string>&ndash;&gt;-->
    <!--&lt;!&ndash;<string name="vinimaya_card2">&ndash;&gt;-->
    <!--&lt;!&ndash;Wait it’s not just books…! VINIMAYA also shares TV series, Anime, Movies, Ted Talks, E-Books for the one who seeks. Any student can drop into G2C2 room and borrow their favourite book, anime, movie, without any membership.&ndash;&gt;-->
    <!--&lt;!&ndash;</string>&ndash;&gt;-->
    <!--&lt;!&ndash;<string name="vinimaya_card3">&ndash;&gt;-->
    <!--&lt;!&ndash;Website: - http://aliengo.000webhostapp.com/first/vini2.0/vini2home.php&ndash;&gt;-->

    <!--&lt;!&ndash;Contact: - Sanjana  (+91 96860 00788)&ndash;&gt;-->
    <!--&lt;!&ndash;</string>&ndash;&gt;-->

    <!--<string name="sae_card1">-->
    <!--Society of automotive Engineers (SAE) is a World-Wide organization which sets standards and validates automotive projects. A student branch of this organization exists in UVCE. The motto of SAE-INDIA stands as ‘The Engineering Society for Advancing Mobility in Land Sea Air and Space’. \n\n-->
    <!--GKDC (go-cart building championship), BAJA (Pronounced as BAHA, is an all-terrain vehicle building championship), SUPRA (Racing car building championship) are the main National Level competition organised by SAE.-->
    <!--</string>-->
    <!--<string name="sae_card2">-->
    <!--The student branch of SAE, ‘SAE-INDIA UVCE’ was set up in 2011 due to the earnest efforts of Mechanical Students of Batch 2009-2013. The club till date has involved in conducting many activities to benefit the members for improving their skills in the technical field. \n\n-->
    <!--Team Em-power UVCE stood 6th (AIR) in GKDC and 124th(AIR) In BAJA are some of the acclaimed achievements of the group till date.-->
    <!--</string>-->
    <!--<string name="sae_card3">-->
    <!--Email: sae.uvce@gmail.com \n\n-->
    <!--Contact: Tejas N  (+91 81234 12123)-->
    <!--</string>-->

    <!--<string name="tatva_card1">-->
    <!--We are aware of the fact that RAMESH ARAVIND, DATTANNA, MANOHMURTHY are namma UVCE’s proud alumni who with their skills have created an everlasting impact on Kannada film industry.\n \nUVCE’s leading collegiate Club which aims to improve one\'s skill in acting is Thathva.-->
    <!--</string>-->
    <!--<string name="tatva_card2">-->
    <!--Thathva was established by Abhishek Chakma from ECE batch of 2015. Currently Thathva consists of 60+ students involved in the activity. Members of Thathva took part in a street play ensemble called Manthan which took place in Forum mall, Kormangala. \n \nThe main objective is to: \n \n-->
    <!--* Promote theatre in college \n-->
    <!--* Set up a platform for theatre enthusiasts\n-->
    <!--* To collaborate and do what they love-->
    <!--</string>-->
    <!--<string name="tatva_card3">-->
    <!--Contact: Rajat  (+91 96868 24746 )-->
    <!--</string>-->

    <!--<string name="g2c2_card1">-->
    <!--To accomplish the purpose of Clean and Green UVCE, a student led initiative, "Go Green and Clean Club" which is simply known as G2C2 was started in the year 2014 by a group of ME CSE department students. It is now run by enthusiasts from 2nd and 3rd year BE students. Presently it has about 100 voluntary members who are dedicated towards the cause.-->
    <!--</string>-->
    <!--<string name="g2c2_card2">-->
    <!--Club aims to involve college faculty, alumni and larger number of students in future days to improve its effectiveness.-->
    <!--</string>-->
    <!--<string name="g2c2_card3">-->
    <!--Email: gogreenuvce@gmail.com \n\n-->
    <!--Contact: Vipasha (+91 88673 19691)-->
    <!--</string>-->

    <!--<string name="ecell_card1">-->
    <!--The Entrepreneurship Cell of UVCE, commonly known as E-Cell UVCE, has been established with the objective of creating, fostering and promoting the spirit of entrepreneurship among the students of UVCE.-->
    <!--</string>-->
    <!--<string name="ecell_card2">-->
    <!--It wants not only to ignite the minds but also to nurture the ideas of one of the most talented students of India.\n\n-->
    <!--E-CELL UVCE is committed to build a strong platform for the budding entrepreneurs.\n\n-->
    <!--The vision is to guide the students to take entrepreneurship as a career, as a path to success, as a journey of wisdom.-->
    <!--</string>-->
    <!--<string name="ecell_card3">-->
    <!--Contact: Chaitra (+91 95910 97654)-->
    <!--</string>-->

    <!--<string name="sports_card1">-->
    <!--Sports at UVCE have remained at its best by the sportsman skill of UVCEians. The physical education department is led by Dr. Lokesh Reddy who is the mentor and monitor of sports at UVCE.-->
    <!--</string>-->
    <!--<string name="sports_card2">-->
    <!--UVCE have its football team and cricket team which is recognized across the state for its excellence in their respective field. Selection process happens once in a year and teams practice in Bangalore University ground located close to UVCE campus.-->
    <!--</string>-->
    <!--<string name="sports_card3">-->
    <!--Contact: Tejasvi P K (+91 91084 56352)-->
    <!--</string>-->


    <!--<string name="dance_card1">-->

    <!--</string>-->
    <!--<string name="dance_card2">-->

    <!--</string>-->
    <!--<string name="dance_card3">-->
    <!--Contact: Tejaswini (+91 97382 83445)-->
    <!--</string>-->

    <!--<string name="music_card1">-->

    <!--</string>-->
    <!--<string name="music_card2">-->

    <!--</string>-->
    <!--<string name="music_card3">-->
    <!--Contact: Sowmya (+91 97435 69412)-->
    <!--</string>-->


</resources>

